If you had a billboard on which you
could put anything non-commercial,
metaphorically to get a message or
something in front of billions of
people, what might you put on that
billboard? Does anything come to mind?
>> I'm going to get very broad on this. Ask
every question. We live in a time of
silence, and that people are leaving
things unquestioned and unspoken. Why is
a pretty good one, too, if you want to
go with that.
>> Why is a good one?
>> Why don't you go why? With the question
mark. Why has it got to be that way?
Just trying to go against an age of
pathological conformity.
>> Yes, often subconscious, too.
Pathological conformity. Ask why. Why
does it have to be this way? Also, with
your own thinking. It applies
everywhere.
>> Everywhere.